[
    {
    "quizName":"Basic Addition",
    "grade":"school",
    "subGrade":"1st",
    "topic":"Arithmetics",
    "quizDisc":"Basic Arithmetics",
    "quizHour":"1",
    "quizMinutes":"30",
    "quizOwner":"chekodu.adarsh@gmail.com",
    "quizTarget":["all"],
    "questions":[
            {
                "question":"1+1?",
                "options":["10","1","2","3","4"],
                "correctAnswer":["2"],
                "score":"1",
                "selected":[]
            },
            {
                "question":"1+2?",
                "options":["10","1","2","3","4"],
                "correctAnswer":["3"],
                "score":"1",
                "selected":[]
            },
            {
                "question":"1+10?",
                "options":["10","1","2","3","4","11"],
                "correctAnswer":["1","11"],
                "score":"2",
                "selected":[]
            },
            {
                "question":"1+0?",
                "options":["0","1"],
                "correctAnswer":["1"],
                "score":"1",
                "selected":[]
            }
        ]      
    },
    {
        "quizName":"Basic Subtraction",
        "grade":"school",
        "subGrade":"1st",
        "topic":"Arithmetics",
        "quizDisc":"Basic Arithmetics",
        "quizHour":"1",
        "quizMinutes":"30",
        "quizOwner":"chekodu.adarsh@gmail.com",
        "quizTarget":["all"],
        "questions":[
            {
                "question":"1-1?",
                "options":["10","1","2","3","4"],
                "correctAnswer":["0"],
                "score":"1",
                "selected":[]
            },
            {
                "question":"2-1?",
                "options":["10","1","2","3","4"],
                "correctAnswer":["1"],
                "score":"1",
                "selected":[]
            },
            {
                "question":"10-8?",
                "options":["10","1","2","3","4","11"],
                "correctAnswer":["2"],
                "score":"2",
                "selected":[]
            },
            {
                "question":"1-0?",
                "options":["0","1"],
                "correctAnswer":["1"],
                "score":"1",
                "selected":[]
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "quizName":"Basic English",
        "grade":"school",
        "subGrade":"1st",
        "topic":"Arithmetics",
        "quizDisc":"Basic Arithmetics",
        "quizHour":"1",
        "quizMinutes":"30",
        "quizOwner":"chekodu.adarsh@gmail.com",
        "quizTarget":["all"],
        "questions":[
            {
                "question":"Appl_?",
                "options":["e","a","o","i","k"],
                "correctAnswer":["e"],
                "score":"1",
                "selected":[]
            },
            {
                "question":"Tre_?",
                "options":["e","a","o","i","y"],
                "correctAnswer":["3"],
                "score":"1",
                "selected":[]
            },
            {
                "question":"M_ngo?",
                "options":["a","b","e","y","k","g"],
                "correctAnswer":["1","11"],
                "score":"2",
                "selected":[]
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "quizName":"Basic division",
        "grade":"school",
        "subGrade":"1st",
        "topic":"Arithmetics",
        "quizDisc":"Basic Arithmetics",
        "quizHour":"1",
        "quizMinutes":"30",
        "quizOwner":"chekodu.adarsh@gmail.com",
        "quizTarget":["all"],
        "questions":[
            {
                "question":"2 / 1?",
                "options":["10","2","0.5","3","4"],
                "correctAnswer":["2"],
                "score":"1",
                "selected":[]
            },
            {
                "question":"1/2?",
                "options":["10","0.5","2","3","4"],
                "correctAnswer":["3"],
                "score":"1",
                "selected":[]
            }
        ]
    }
]